准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
钩子
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
客串
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
渔夫对于我们的海底朋友
Fishermen have quite an effect
有着不小的影响
on our undersea friends
蟹堡王
海绵宝宝  你擦完甲板了吗
SpongeBob, have you finished swabbing the deck?
快了
Almost
九号桌底下有个难搞的藤壶
There's a nasty barnacle under table nine
它们回来了
They're back
跟你们说  它们回来了
They're back, I tell you
我亲眼看见的
I saw with my own eyes
钩子
The hooks
能不能吃个口香糖
How about a mint?
钩子
The hooks
可不可以打包外带
Can you make that to go?
你都不知道自己运气有多好
You don't know how lucky you are
钩子
The hooks
我本来在
So there I was
干我自己的事
minding my own business
我是很想再听你讲精彩的海底故事
I'd love to hear another of your riveting sea tales
可是
but, um
我得去检查我垃圾桶了
I have to do my wastebasket inspections
对  里面有东西
Oh, yeah, there's one
好
Fine
可别说我没警告过你
Don't say I didn't warn you
警告他什么  蟹老板
Warn him about what, Mr. Krabs?
是钩子  我的小子
The hooks, me bucko
它们回来了
They're back
小心钩子
Beware the hooks
钩子
The hooks?
对  钩子
Aye, the hooks
它们会垂下来
They dangle down
用愉悦的形状和诱人的颜色勾引你
and draw you close with their pleasing shapes
and their beguiling colors
等到你自以为找到了一片乐土
And just when you think
you found the land of milk and honey
它们就会就会扒你裤子
they grab you by the britches
高高地把你拉上天
and haul you way up high
然后再高
Then higher
再高
and higher
直到把你拉到海面之上
until you're hauled up to the surface
四处扑腾  大口喘气
flopping and gasping for breath
然后那些东西就会把你做成吃的吃掉
And then they cook you and then they eat you
或者更惨
Or worse
还会有什么东西比那更惨
What could be worse than that?
礼品店
Gift shops
海星
各色贝壳
不要让它抓到我  蟹老板
Don't let it get me, Mr. Krabs
好了  小子
There, there, boy
它们不会抓到你的
they won't get you
好好听蟹老板的话就不会有事
Not as long as you listen to old Mr. Krabs
快回厨房去
Now get back to the kitchen
时间就是金钱
Time is money
遵命  蟹老板
Aye-aye, Mr. Krabs
早安  蟹堡王的员工
Good morning, Krusty crew
嗨  派大星
Hey, Patrick
猜怎么着
Guess what?
嘉年华来城里了
The carnival's in town
快一起过去吧
Come on, let's go
我还不能走  我在上班
I can't leave now, I'm working
这可不算走  你那算休息
It's not leaving, you're just taking a break
我们要去嘉年华  要去嘉年
We're going to the carnival, going to the carniv
我们要去嘉年华  要去嘉年华
We're going to the carnival, going to the carnival
到了  海绵宝宝
There it is, SpongeBob
嘉年华回城里了
The carnival is back in town
我要排第一个  把所有项目都玩一遍
I'm going to be first in line for everything
大家都哪去了
Where is everybody?
不知道
I don't know
早些时候有个小朋友来过
There was one kid here earlier
样子感觉不像我玩过的嘉年
Doesn't look like any carnival I ever
不好意思
Excuse me
别去  派大星
Stop, Patrick
别去摸
Don't touch it
这不是嘉年华  派大星
This isn't the carnival, Patrick
是钩子
Those are hooks
蟹老板说钩子特别危险
Mr. Krabs says they're really dangerous
我没感觉到危险
I sense no danger here
这些东西怎么会危险呢
How could they be dangerous?
上面还放着白送的奶酪呢
They're covered with free cheese
我只知道蟹老板说过
All I know is, Mr. Krabs said
派大星
Patrick
别那样
Don't do that
奶酪味
Cheesy
没有危险
No danger here
快来试试看
Go on, try it
可蟹老板说过
But Mr. Krabs said
海绵宝宝  我来问问你
SpongeBob, let me ask you something
这看起来危险吗
Does this look dangerous?
派大星
Patrick
不要
Don't
能不能放松点
Lighten up, will you?
还是说得要我自个把奶酪全吃
Or do I have to eat all this cheese by mysel
派大星
Patrick
救命啊
Help
派大星
Patrick
救命啊
Help
派大星  回来吧
Patrick, come back
我最好的朋友
My best friend
派大星  你还活着
Patrick, you're alive
那当然了
Am I ever
你得来试试看
You should try it
可是怎么对付海平面的事
But what about the surface
还有裤子的事
and your britches
还有礼品店的事
and the gift shops?
趁升得还不算高赶紧跳下去
You just jump off before you go up too high
蟹老板交代过我不该靠近那些东西的
Mr. Krabs said I shouldn't get near those things
那他说过你不应该爬上去
Did he say you shouldn't climb on top of them
然后当马骑吗
and ride them like a horsy?
没有
Well, no
估计是没说过
I guess he didn't
衣鱼
Silverfish
出发
Away
准备好了吗
Ready?
准备好了
Ready
杰罗尼莫
Geronimo
[ Geronimo：感叹词，尤在从高空跳下时喊出 ]
比在蟹堡王加班好玩多了
This is more fun
than double overtime at the Krusty Krab
蟹堡王
恶心
P.U.
你管这叫吃的
You call this food?
我三明治味道像炸靴子
My sandwich tastes like a fried boot
我三明治就是个炸靴子
My sandwich is a fried boot
能不能做快点
Hurry it up, will you
我们都饿坏了  看看大家
We're hungry over here, look at us
我孩子啥都吃不到  让我都快没命了
My kids haven't eaten and I'll die
你这么翻肉饼不对
That's not how you're supposed to flip it
你们干什么非得吃这种东西
Why do you want to eat this stuff anyway?
章鱼哥先生
Mr. Squidward
这到底怎么回事
What the halibut's going on in here?
大家争着想要吃的  老板
It's a feeding frenzy, sir
而且海绵宝宝还没休息完
and SpongeBob's not back from his break
什么
What?
我还以为你说海绵宝宝在休息
I thought you said SpongeBob was taking a break
自从59年的海霸大饥荒以来
No one's taken a break at the Krusty Krab
所有人都不让休息
since the chum famine of '59
你刚刚说什么来着
Now, what were you saying?
他去
He took
休息了
a break
好  懒鬼宝宝
All right, SpongeBob lazypants
我要找到你
I'll find you
我这鼻子能闻到一万里格远的懒鬼味
This nose can smell laziness for up to 10,000 leagues
我倒要给你好好休息一场
I'll give you a break
好让你永生难忘
you'll not soon forget
可是蟹老板  我需要人帮忙
But Mr. Krabs, I still need help
应该就在这
They should be right here
再来吗
Again?
再来
Again
钩子
The hooks
不不不
No, no, no
一  二  三
One, two, three
等等  等等
Wait, wait
小子
Boys
我还是慢了一步
I wasn't quick enough
他们就这么没了
They're gone
要是我能再把他抱进怀里的话
If I could only hold him in me arms again
我  我就
I, I'd
就狠狠把他们掐住
I'd throttle them
我是怎么跟你交代钩子的事的  小子
What did I tell you about those hooks, boy?
我
I, uh
I
我来跟你们说说钩子的事
I'll tell you about the hooks
要骑上钩子升升升
You ride them up and up and up
然后慢慢地飘下来
then you gently float down
知不知道飘不回来会出什么事吗
And do you know what happens
when you don't float back down?
礼品店
Gift shop?
更惨
Worse
到头来你们会被真空包装
You end up vacuum-packed
塞进金枪鱼罐头里
in a can of tuna
金枪鱼
日子完全没盼头
With nothing to look forward to
只能闻蛋黄酱的味道
but the smell of mayonnaise
蛋黄酱
对不起  蟹老板
We're sorry, Mr. Krabs
你们几个小子得向我保证
I want you boys to promise me
再也不去骑那些钩子
you'll never go on those hooks again
我们保证  蟹老板
We promise, Mr. Krabs
我要的是水手宣誓
I need a sailor's promise
跟着我做
Repeat after me
我不会再靠近钩子
Near the hooks I'll never go
我们不会再靠近钩子
Near the hooks we'll never go
珍珍的妈啊
Mother of pearl
甲板起火了
Fire on the poop deck
珍珍的妈啊
Mother of pearl
甲板起火了
Fire on the poop deck
好
Well
那好吧
All right, then
赶快离开这个死亡陷阱
Let's get out of this deathtrap anyway
好了  小蜗
Okay, Gary
今天是全新的一天
today is a new day
我准备好向蟹老板证明自己很忠诚了
I'm ready to prove myself loyal to Mr. Krabs
我准备好了
I'm ready
嗨  海绵宝宝
Hey, SpongeBob
你走错路了
You're going the wrong way
我上班向来都走这条路
I always go to work this way
你今天不用上班
You're not going to work today
我们要去玩
We're going to go play
钩子
hooky
可是派大星  我们宣过誓的
But, Patrick, we promised
我手指交叉  运气可好了
I had my fingers crossed
你根本就没手指  派大星
You don't have fingers, Patrick
那个蟹老板就是个大笨蛋
Well, that Mr. Krabs is just a big dummy
咱都玩钩子玩一整天了
We played on those hooks all day long
也没出过什么事
and nothing happened to us
可蟹老板说
But Mr. Krabs said
听好  海绵宝宝
Look, SpongeBob
你是要听大笨蛋的话
Are you going to listen to a big dummy
还是要听我的话
or are you going to listen to me?
等会见  海绵宝宝
See you later, SpongeBob
我要去痛快玩耍了
I'm going to go have some fun
快来  海绵宝宝
Come on, SpongeBob
你知道你很想
You know you want to
我知道我很想
I know I want to
可我跟蟹老板宣过誓
but I promised Mr. Krabs
不会再去靠近
I wouldn't go near another
钩子
Hook
不行
Oh, no
蟹老板跟我说过你的事
Mr. Krabs told me all about you
你是个大骗子  谎话精
You are a liar, a deceiver
我绝对不会再中你的圈套
I'll never fall for your tricks again
绝不
Never
这个位子有人坐吗
Is this seat taken?
真高兴摆脱了想玩钩子的感觉
Glad I got that out of my system
我被
I'm
钩住了
hooked
这就表示
And that means
金枪鱼
救命
Help
我被钩住了
I'm hooked
救命
Help
蟹老板  救命
Mr. Krabs, help
出事了
It happened
我被钩住了
I'm hooked
不
Oh, no
钩子
the hook
礼品店
Gift shop
金枪鱼罐头
Tuna can
蛋黄酱
Mayonnaise
拿去吧  珍珍
Here you go, Pearl
给你朋友喝的免费白水
Free water for all your little friends
谢谢了  爸
Thanks, dad
别忘了给蟹老板留个小费
Just don't forget to leave a tip for old Mr. Krabs
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
你都迟到两分钟了
You're two minutes late
你干什么迟到了  小子
What kept you, laddie?
你知道我们昨天谈到过的钩子吗
You know those hooks we were talking about yesterday?
我没告诉过你不要靠近钩子吗
Didn't I tell you not to go near those hooks?
没
No
我是说有  有
I mean yes, yes
你告诉过我不要靠近钩子
you told me not to go near them
你没坐钩子上玩吧
Well, you weren't playing on those hooks
对吧  小子
were you, laddie?
当然没
Of course not
我是说  算是没
I mean, not exactly
我是说  我坐了
I mean, yes
对  我坐上去玩了
Yes, I did it
我承认了
I admit it
蟹老板  我好羞愧
Mr. Krabs, I'm so ashamed
我是说  看看我
I mean, look at me
我被钩住了
I'm hooked
钩得还挺深
It's in there pretty deep
要怎么办才好
What am I going to do?
只有一个办法了  小子
There's only one thing to do, boy
不行  蟹老板
Oh, no, Mr. Krabs
不能脱裤子
I can't take off my pants
绝对不能面对着这群
Not in front of all these
女生
girls
好  我这就脱
Okay, I'm taking them off
这就脱
I'm taking them off
好了
There
小子
Lad
不行
Oh, no
不不不
No, no, no
蟹老板  我不行
Mr. Krabs, I can't do it
那种事绝对不行
Anything but that
我能理解
I understand
你是个不错的煎炸厨师  海绵宝宝
You were a good little fry cook, SpongeBob
招聘
不过咱会另外招人的
But we'll find another
但愿能招到能听蟹老板话的人
Hopefully, one that will listen to old Mr. Krabs
蟹老板  我会听话的
Mr. Krabs, I'll listen
我保证
I promise
求你救救我  蟹老板
Please save me, Mr. Krabs
我保证我会表现好的
I promise I'll be good
快看
Look
是光身子宝宝
It's SpongeBob nudiepants
海绵宝宝这种模样我可太想看了
Well, that was more of SpongeBob than I needed to see
章鱼哥先生  你钓鱼技术实在是高
Mr. Squidward, that was some fine angling
你觉得那小子学到教训了吗
Do you think the lad has learned his lesson?
我想他会记得非常久的
I think he'll remember this for a long time
穿裤子
The pants
起码我肯定会
I know I will
穿内裤
The underwear
有人吗
Hello?
金枪鱼
有谁有开罐器的吗
Does somebody have a can opener?
美人鱼战士
和企鹅男孩
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
客串
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
裤头村周六的早上
Saturday morning in bikini bottom
海绵宝宝正看着
SpongeBob is watching
他最爱的周六早间节目
his favorite Saturday morning show
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩的冒险
the adventures of Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
美人鱼战士
和企鹅男孩
麦麸片
吃着美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩麦麸片
Enjoying a bowl of
Mermaidman and Barnacleboy bran cereal
戴着美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩官方正品
And wearing the official Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
早餐假牙
breakfast biters
美人鱼战士  敏捷又强大
Mermaidman, fleet and forceful
赐予我海神王的力量
by the power of Neptune
有他的年轻小跟班相助
Aided by his young ward
aided by his young ward
用敏捷又强大的技艺保护海洋
Protecting the sea with feats of strength and agility
前往推拿店
To the chiropractor
出发
Away
对抗一大批大坏蛋
Fighting a rogues gallery of villains
比如邪恶臭蛞蝓
like the sinister slug
道具
原子比目鱼
The atomic flounder
纸板
以及可怕巨霸虾
and the dreaded jumbo shrimp
逊
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩合为一体
Mermaidman and Barnacleboy unite
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
小朋友们
Hey, kids
准备好要揭晓本周大赛的优胜者了吗
are you ready to hear the winner of this week's contest?
我准备好了
I'm ready
优胜者将会赢得
Our winner will receive
一样特别机密珍藏品
a special secret collector's item
出自美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩的冒险
from the adventures of Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
优胜者是
And the winner is
黑面宝宝
Springboob Squirepin
我特地做美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
I worked forever
on those life-size Krabby Patty mannequins
等身蟹黄堡模型做了好久
of Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
他制作了美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
for these life-size Krabby Patty mannequins
等身蟹黄堡模型
of Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
黑面宝宝盗了我的创意
Springboob Squirepin stole my idea
说什么
What's that?
看来刚刚不小心念错名字了
It appears I've made a slight error in pronunciation
优胜者的真正大名是
The real name of the winner is
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
想知道我奖品什么时候
I wonder when my prize will
会到
get here
我的奖品
my prize
会不会是
Can it be?
就是
It is
海螺号角
The conch signal
出自美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩的冒险
From the adventures of Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
跟电视上的一个样
As seen on TV
想知道还能不能用
I wonder if it still works?
荫凉滩疗养院
海螺号角
The conch signal
前往无影船
To the invisible boatmobile
美人鱼战士
Mermaidman?
怎么了  企鹅男孩
Yes, Barnacleboy?
我们是不是还没上无影船
We're not in the invisible boatmobile, are we?
没上
Nope
早跟你说过
I told you
把船做成无影这种事特别傻
making the boatmobile invisible was a stupid idea
快出来  快出来
Come out, come out
不管你在哪
wherever you are
肯定就在这附近
It's got to be here somewhere
美人鱼战士  我好像
Oh, Mermaidman, I think I
找到了
Found it
快点上车  孩子
Come on, get a move on, son
我们时间不多
We don't have all day
点火
Ignition on
加速
Throttle up
可能海螺号角用不了了
maybe the conch signal doesn't work anymore
激活鱼雷模式
Activate torpedo mode
发射
Fire
美人鱼战士
Mermaidman
还有七鹅男
And bobicle bob
真不敢相信  小蜗
I can't believe it, Gary
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩来咱家了
Mermaidman and Barnacleboy in our home
不好意思  我
Excuse me, I'm
我的海神王啊
Oh, my Neptune
他已经毁容得不成样子了
He's been horribly disfigured
太糟了
Blast us
我们来太迟了
We're too late
真是的
Oh, please
他没毁容
He's not disfigured
他就  就
he's, he's
又是那个海绵小子
just that sponge kid again
对啊
Oh, yeah
很高兴再见到你  小子
Good to see you, lad
企鹅男孩  我们一定要找出
Say, Barnacleboy, we've got to find out
海螺号角的声音是哪发出来的
where that conch signal came from
是我发的
That was me
海螺号角就是我吹的
I blew the conch signal, sir
好
All right
哪里有危险  孩子
Where's the danger, son?
快放马过来
Bring it on
放马过来
不用担心
Don't worry
没有危险
There's no danger
没危险
No danger?
听好  一定得有危险
Look, there has to be danger
你都吹了海螺号角
You blew the conch signal
吹的时候
and when you blow
你到底是怎么弄到那东西的
Where did you get that thing anyway?
我参加大赛赢来的
I won it in a contest
大赛
Contest?
节目组什么事都没跟咱说啊
They don't tell us anything anymore
听好  海绵宝宝
Look, Spongy
那不是玩具
that ain't no toy
没错
That's right--
海螺号角可是个重责大任
The conch signal is an awesome responsibility
每当它响起  我们都会挺身出手相助
We're duty-bound to help whenever it sounds
但是你只能遇到麻烦了再吹
But you only blow it when there's trouble
否则就会出现麻烦  明白吗
or there will be trouble, you got that?
明白  先生们
Yes, sirs
好孩子
Good boy
快点
Come on
今天疗养院卖肉糕
They're serving meat loaf today
好耶
Oh, goody
你放心  美人鱼战士
Don't worry, Mermaidman
我绝不会随便出什么事就吹海螺号角
You won't be hearing from me for just anything
只会在重大紧急情况才吹
Only for the big emergencies
能不能洗快点
Will you hurry up in there?
顺便给我省点热水
And save me some hot water
海螺号角
The conch signal
快来  年轻小跟班
Come, young ward
年轻人
Youth
还朝气蓬勃的  就这么没了
Cut down in its prime
说句话  孩子
Speak to me, son
救命
Help
没办法
Can't
开蛋黄酱
Open mayonnaise
蛋黄酱
什么
What?
我只穿着内裤来这
I come down here in my underwear
就是来开蛋黄酱罐子的吗
to open a jar of mayonnaise?
但是
But
没有但是
But nothing
我们不能到处走  跟别人交往
We can't go around socializing
我们必须准备好应对
We have to be prepared for, uh
紧急情况
emergencies
企鹅男孩  你想想看
Barnacleboy, think about it
紧急情况现在也不是很经常出现了
Emergencies don't come around as often as they used to
好  行
All right, okay
你可以偶尔吹一次海螺号角
You can blow the conch every once in a while
等我们来就给咱事情做
just give us something to do when we show up
危险
Danger
好  都够了
All right, that's it
快给我
Give me that
你害我们都累垮了
You're running us ragged
一定要
Must
一定要响应号角的号召
must answer the clarion call
我们累坏了
We're exhausted
对不起  企鹅男孩
I'm sorry, Barnacleboy
我不是有意的  我
I didn't mean it, I
只是想陪着你们
just wanted to spend time with you
你们是我的英雄
You're my heroes
说这些都太晚了  大赛优胜者先生
It's too late for that, Mr. Contest winner
我要毁掉这个东西  用我的
I'm going to destroy this thing with my
硫光眼
sulfur vision
好吧  毁掉它的事
Well, I'll destroy it
还是等到回
when I get back to the, uh
美人鱼基地再说
mermalair
至于你
And as for you
企鹅男孩
Barnacleboy
不要打击他的热情
don't squash his enthusiasm
毕竟  他可能会当上明天的英雄
After all, he could be the hero of tomorrow
也可能会当上坏蛋
or the villain
并且
Besides
我还记得还有个年轻狂小子
I remember another young whippersnapper
想当个超级英雄呢
who wanted to be a super-hero
你连吃早饭都不记得  老东西
You don't even remember breakfast, you old coot
可能海螺号角蕴含着的责任太重大
Maybe the conch signal is too much responsibility
不过你想不想下午后面的时间一起来
But how would you like to spend
the rest of the afternoon
巡逻
on patrol?
什么
What?
前往无影船
To the invisible boatmobile
叮叮当
Jingle bells
美人鱼战士臭  企鹅男孩下了蛋
Mermaidman smells, Barnacleboy laid an egg
行
无影船少了个轮胎  而且
The invisible boatmobile lost a wheel and
停
我能开吗
Can I drive?
开船
Drive?
你知道要怎么开无影船吗
What do you know about
driving the invisible boatmobile?
知道不少呢
Tons
比如说雨刮器在这
Like the windshield wipers are right here
不要碰那个按钮
Don't touch that button
那可是
It's the
折纸按钮
origami button
在城市里巡逻的时候
When you're patrolling the city
一定要谨慎
you always have to be vigilant
时时刻刻保持警惕
On your toes, constantly alert
确保有备无患
Always expect the unexpected
我买到甜甜圈了
I've got the donuts
企鹅男孩下了蛋
And Barnacle Boy laid an egg
那边那位以前是原子比目鱼
That fellow over there used to be the atomic flounder
我知道他看着不太像
I know he doesn't look like much
但是他很有可能会回归犯罪
but he could go back to crime
猝不及防
just like that
救命
Help
公交站
救命  谁来救救我
Help, somebody there
你被捕了  原子比目鱼
You're under arrest, atomic flounder
住手  孩子
Stop, kid
住手
stop
放他走
Let him go
你说他可能会失控
You said he could snap
猝不及防
just like that
什么
What?
给我下去
Get off of me
要不是我退休了  我早
If I weren't retired, I
我早就
I'd
这样
Do that
快滚开  混账
Out of my way, punk
小餐馆
真不敢相信
I can't believe it
我坐着无影船兜风
I rode in the invisible boatmobile
碰到了个坏蛋
met a villain
还学会处理三度烧伤
and learned to treat third-degree burns
一天就办这么多事
all in one day
那我们明天要干什么
So what are we gonna do tomorrow?
我说  孩子
Say, kid
你要不然拿着这一毛钱去那边
why don't you take this nickel and go over there
看看点唱机上面有没有我们的主题曲
and see if our theme song is on the jukebox?
好
Okay
你要知道  他作为一个讨厌鬼
You know, for a pain in the neck
还是个很棒的孩子
he's a pretty nice kid
快甩了他吧
Let's ditch him
你先走  我殿后
Right behind you
点唱机好像没主题曲
It doesn't seem to be here
肯定会有的
It's there, all right
继续找
Keep looking
加把劲  加把劲
Diligence, diligence
遵命  长官
Aye-aye, sir
该死
Dagnabbit
怎么了
What's the matter?
我们刚把无影船停哪了
Where did we park the invisible boatmobile?
我都找第15遍了
That's the 15th time I've looked
但我绝不能让我英雄们失望
But I can't let my heroes down
无影船
Boatmobile?
你在哪
Where are you?
企鹅男孩  我找到了
Barnacleboy, I found it
尾气管又把你烧伤了是吗  企鹅男孩
Still getting burned
on that tailpipe, huh, Barnacleboy?
是肮脏泡泡
It's the dirty bubble
又脏又圆地冒出来了
In all his dirty roundness
不
Oh, no
我找到了
I found it
还是特别舞曲混音版
And it's the special dance mix
救命
Help
我的蟹黄堡啊
Holy krabby patties
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩的死对头
Mermaidman and Barnacleboy's archnemesis
肮脏泡泡
The dirty bubble
真不敢相信
I can't believe it
你绝对救不回他们  神秘海绵
You cannot save them, sponge of mystery
他们被我超强的表面张力困住了
They are trapped by my awesome surface tension
你不明白
You don't understand
你可是我最爱的超级坏蛋
You're my most favorite supervillain
能给我签个名吗
Can I have your autograph?
不行
Oh, no
不行  你这笨蛋
Oh, no, you fool
退后
Stay back
笔尖
The point
小心笔尖
Watch the point
你救了我们  孩子
You saved us, son
对  你是
Yeah, you're
你是个英雄
you're a hero
是吗
I am?
要再来坐着无影船兜风吗
Are you up for another ride
in the invisible boatmobile?
叮叮当  美人鱼战士臭
Jingle bells, Mermaidman smells
企鹅男孩下了蛋
Barnacleboy laid an egg
肮脏泡泡被扎破
The dirty bubble popped
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
And Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
还有海绵宝宝逃出生天
and SpongeBob got away
小心点
Watch out